const quizData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of fasting in Islam?",
    answers: [
      "Don't eat anything all day",
      "Relax your body and mind",
      "Losing weight",
      "Self-control, reinforces one's faith and piety",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Why muslim people fast during Ramadan?",
    answers: [
      "Cultural Behavior",
      "It is Prophet Mohammed's duty",
      "It is one of the 5 pillars of Islam",
      "Because everyone fasting during Ramadan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "When do Muslims fast during Ramadan?",
    answers: [
      "From Dawn to Sunset",
      "From Sunset to Dawn",
      "From Morning to Afternoon",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which is allowed for the Muslims during the fasting?",
    answers: ["Chewing gum", "Drinking", "Eating", "No one"],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which is not allowed for the Muslims during the fasting?",
    answers: ["Napping", "To Hug", "Smoking", "Brushing teeth"],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What do you do if you accidentally eat/drink while fasting?",
    answers: [
      "There is nothing to do, continue to eat",
      "Continue your fast, it is a gift from Allah",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What do you do if you eat/drink consciously without any reason while fasting?",
    answers: [
      "Continue your fast if no one sees you",
      "You need to fast 60 days after the Ramadan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the evening meal end of fasting?",
    answers: ["Sahur", "Iftar", "Dinner"],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How many days are there in Ramadan?",
    answers: ["30-31 days", "29-30 days", "39-40 days"],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who is exempt from fasting during Ramadan??",
    answers: [
      "Sick People",
      "Pregnant Women",
      "Old People",
      "Children",
      "All Above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What can you do instead if you are unable to fast?",
    answers: [
      "Do it later",
      "Pray to Allah for forgiveness",
      "Feed a needy person, or give in charity to the poor",
      "Sacrifice a ship or a goat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "How do the Muslim people break fast?",
    answers: [
      "With soup and milk",
      "With bread and water",
      "With date and water",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What is the pre-dawn meal known?",
    answers: ["Iftar", "Sahur", "Breakfast"],
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "What significant event took place in the last 10 days of Ramadan according to Islam?",
    answers: [
      "The Holy Kabbah was built",
      "Prophet Muhammad was born",
      "The Holy Quran was first revealed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Ramadan is a month of: ",
    answers: ["Prayer", "Fasting", "Charity", "Gratitude", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "Which country is fasting the longest in 2024? (17 hours 52 minutes on the last day of Ramadan) ",
    answers: ["Saudi Arabia", "Qatar", "Netherlands", "Greenland"],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "What is the Obligatory Charity which is paid in the form of peopleâ€™s staple food or grains before the Eid Prayers? ",
    answers: ["Sadaqah", "It is not required to pay charity", "Zakat-al-Fitr"],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Which festival is celebrated after the month of fasting? ",
    answers: [
      "Eid-al-Fitr",
      "Eid-al-Adha",
      "There is no festival after the month of fasting",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "How does a meat or chicken become halal? ",
    answers: [
      "It must be washed",
      "It must come from certain area",
      "It must be blessed",
      "It must sacrificed in a muslim country",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Which one is halal for Muslims? ",
    answers: [
      "Every chicken is halal",
      "Pork",
      "%0 alcohol beer",
      "Fish",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
];

export default quizData;
